A Guide to the Herbert E. Harris II Papers
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- Series III: Legislation Files
  - Subseries A: Legislative Information Files
    - H Res 688: Pay adjustments for Federal employees file 1 (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 688: Pay adjustments for Federal employees file 2 (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 805: United Nations equating Zionism with racism (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 951: Select committee on Nuclear Proliferation (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 984: Angola (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 1521: To require Commit. approval certain travel proposals (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 1564: Expressing House of Representatives condemn murders of Letelier and Ronnie Moffitt (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 87: Cosponsored - 1/4/77 Amend Rule XXII - Limit number of members (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 137: Cosponsored - 1/19/77 Exempt motor gas from price regulations (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 138: Cosponsored - 1/19/77 Exempt motor gas from allocation regulations (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 215: Cosponsored - 1/31/77 Support President's nuclear test ban (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 257: Cosponsored - 2/7/77 Prohibit members use of funds (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 323: Cosponsored - 2/23/77 Verbatim account in Congressional Record (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 339: Cosponsored - 2/28/77 Committee approval of travel proposals (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 377: Cosponsored - 3/3/77 Provide for TV and radio coverage (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 462: Cosponsored - 3/22/77 Solar energy in House office buildings (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 475: Cosponsored - 4/5/77 Committee on Population (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 532: Cosponsored - 4/29/77 Solidarity Sunday, May 1, 1977 (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 722: Cosponsored - to establish Commission on South Korean Influence (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 1185: Cosponsored - provide changes for LBJ interns (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 1336: Sponsored - 9/6/78 Disapprove alternative plan for pay federal employees (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 1400: Cosponsored - 10/4/78 House recognize contribution of Bernard de Galyez (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 17: Cosponsored - 7/25/79 Most Favored Nation status to Romania (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 39: Cosponsored - 1/15/79 Establish a select committee on inflation (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 106: Cosponsored - 1/25/79 West Germany should abolish statute of limitations on war crimes (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 146: Cosponsored - 2/27/79 Ratification of the United Nations Convention on Genocide pact (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 232: Cosponsored - 4/23/79 Resolution of Congressional support of Solidarity Sunday (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 292: Cosponsored - 9/4/80 Fair employment relations in the House (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 347: Cosponsored - 7/25/79 Concern for Soviet prisoners of conscience (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 446: Sponsored - 10/16/79 To restrict amendments to appropriations (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 446: Cosponsored - 10/24/79 (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 502: Cosponsored - 12/5/79 Urging Senate action on Windfall prof. (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 618: Cosponsored - 4/21/80 Disapproval of fee on crude oil & gas (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 636: Cosponsored - 4/16/80 Support for Iran sanctions (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 689: Cosponsored - 5/13/80 Congratulations to handicapped Olympic team (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 693: Cosponsored - 6/3/80 Opposition to age discrimination in Federal judge selection (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 698: Cosponsored - 6/4/80 75th anniversary of Sons of Italy (Box Box 81)
    - H Res 756: Cosponsored - 7/28/80 National & Dulles growth and balance policy (Box Box 81)
  - Subseries B: Subject Files
    - Administrative Law Judges HR5723, 1974-1977 (Box Box 82)
    - Administrative Law Judges HR5723, 1977-1978 (Box Box 82)
    - Administrative Law Judges HR5723, 1976-1978 (Box Box 82)
    - Administrative Law Judges HR5723, 1977-1978 (Box Box 82)
    - Air Force - Contracting, Background, 1973-1978 (Box Box 82)
    - Airport Noise - General, 1976-1980 (Box Box 83)
    - Airport Noise - Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box Box 83)
    - Airport Noise - Legislation, 1979-1980 (Box Box 83)
    - Airport Noise - Master File & Studies, 1977-1980 (Box Box 83)
    - Airport Noise - National Airport, 1979-1980 (Box Box 84)
    - Alexandria Rape Victim Companion Program, 1975-1976 (Box Box 84)
    - Alexandria's Retired Senior Volunteer Program, 1978 (Box Box 84)
    - Arms Embargo (Turkey), 1978 (Box Box 84)
    - Army - Contracting, Background, 1976-1978, n.d. (Box Box 84)
    - City of Alexandria, 1975-1976 (Box Box 84)
    - Civil Service Commission, 1977 (Box Box 85)
    - Civil Service Reform - Legislation, 1978 (Box Box 85)
    - Civil Service Reform - General, 1978 (Box Box 85)
    - Contracting in Government Agencies, 1967-1978 (Box Box 85)
    - Committee on the Judiciary, 1980; (2 folders of 3 folders) (Box Box 85)
    - Committee on the Judiciary, 1980; (folder 3 of 3 folders) (Box Box 86)
    - Credit for Volunteer Work - House Concurrent Resolution 11, 1977-1978 (Box Box 86)
    - Dale City Post Office: Prince William County, 1975-1976 (Box Box 86)
    - Department of Defense - Contracting, General Background, 1966-1968, 1974-1977 (Box Box 86)
    - District of Columbia Affairs, 1975-1976; (3 folders of 4 folders) (Box Box 86)
    - District of Columbia Affairs, 1975-1976; (folder 4 of 4 folders) (Box Box 87)
    - District of Columbia: Computer Tax Proposal, 1975-1976 (Box Box 87)
    - Fairfax County: Draft Environmental Impact Statement, Fort Belvoir, 1975-1976 (Box Box 87)
    - Federal Agencies, 1975-1979 (Box Box 87)
    - Federal Employees - General, 1976-1978 (Box Box 87)
    - Federal Employees - Legislation, 1976-1978 (Box Box 88)
    - Federal Employees - Pay, 1975-1977 (Box Box 88)
    - Federal Election Campaign Act, 1976 (Box Box 88)
    - Federal Firefighters' Basic Work Week, 1974-1976, n.d. (Box Box 88)
    - Federal Firefighters' Basic Work Week, 1977-1978, n.d. (Box Box 88)
    - Federal Judgeship Bill, 1977 (Box Box 88)
    - Federal Parking, 1979-1980 (Box Box 89)
    - Federal Physicians, 1975-1978, n.d. (Box Box 89)
    - Flexible Work Hours Act, 1974-1977 (Box Box 89)
    - Form Letters, 1975-1978 (Box Box 89)
    - "G-4" Bill, 1978-1980 (Box Box 89)
    - Gasoline Shortage in Washington Area - Background Information, 1978-1980; (folder 1 of 2 folders) (Box Box 89)
    - Gasoline Shortage in Washington Area - Background Information, 1978-1980; (folder 2 of 2 folders) (Box Box 90)
    - Gasoline Shortage in Washington Area - Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box Box 90)
    - Gasoline Shortage in Washington Area - Washington, D.C. Ruling, 1980 (Box Box 90)
    - Homeowners Relief Act, 1975-1977 (Box Box 90)
    - Impact Aid - Correspondence, 1975-1980 (Box Box 90)
    - Impact Aid - 95th Congress, 1977-1978 (Box Box 90)
    - Impact Aid, 1976-1978 (Box Box 90)
    - Impact Aid, 1978 (Box Box 91)
    - Impact Aid, 1979-1981 (Box Box 91)
    - Intergovernmental Personnel Act - General, 1976-1979 (Box Box 91)
    - Intergovernmental Personnel Act - Background, 1977-1978 (Box Box 91)
    - Intergovernmental Personnel Act - Bills, 1975-1979 (Box Box 91)
    - Intergovernmental Personnel Act - Mobility, 1975-1977 (Box Box 92)
    - Intergovernmental Personnel Act - Operations, 1974 (Box Box 92)
    - Intergovernmental Personnel Act - Reports, 1976-1977 (Box Box 92)
    - Legislative Profile, 1979 Jan-1980 Oct (Box Box 92)
    - Middle East Arms Sales, 1978 (Box Box 92)
    - Miscellaneous, 1976-1980; (2 folders) (Box Box 93)
    - National Demonstration Water Project, 1977-1978 (Box Box 93)
    - Navy - Contracting, Background, 1976-1977 Mar (Box Box 93)
    - Navy - Contracting, Background, 1977 Apr-1978 (Box Box 93)
    - Nonappropriated Fund Administrative Employees (NAF), 1973-1978 (Box Box 94)
    - Nuclear Power, 1979-1980 (Box Box 94)
    - Personnel Ceilings, 1965-1969 May (Box Box 94)
    - Postal Charity, 1977 (Box Box 94)
    - Post Office and Civil Service, 1978 (Box Box 94)
    - Personnel Ceilings, 1969 Jun-1978 (Box Box 95)
    - Request Logs, 1975 (Box Box 95)
    - Revenue Sharing, 1979-1980 (Box Box 95)
    - Rules Changes, 1976-1980 (Box Box 95)
    - Social Security, 1977-1978 (Box Box 95)
    - Supergrade Increase - Requests, 1978; (folder 1 of 2 folders) (Box Box 95)
    - Supergrade Increase - Requests, 1978; (folder 2 of 2 folders) (Box Box 96)
    - Transportation, 1980 (Box Box 96)
    - Virginia Cares, 1979-1980 (Box Box 96)
    - Wang Issue Letter - Commissaries Support, 1975 (Box Box 96)
    - Wang Issue Letter, 1975; (folder 1 of 4 folders) (Box Box 96)
    - Wang Issue Letter, 1975; (3 folders of 4 folders) (Box Box 97)
    - White House Staff, 1977-1978 (Box Box 97)
    - White House Staff - Correspondence & Report, 1978 (Box Box 98)
    - White House Staff - Legislation, 1977-1978 (Box Box 98)
    - WMATA: Metro Transit Police, 1978 (Box Box 98)
    - Year-end Spending - Amendments, 1976-1980 (Box Box 98)
    - Year-end Spending - Background Information, 1979-1980 (Box Box 98)
    - Year-end Spending - Hearings, 1980; (2 folders) (Box Box 99)
    - Year-end Spending Legislation, 1980 (Box Box 99)
  - Subseries C: Chronological Files
    - 1976 Sep-1977 Mar (Box Box 100)
    - 1977 Apr -May (Box Box 100)
    - 1977 Jun -Jul (Box Box 100)
    - 1977 Aug -Dec (Box Box 100)
    - 1978 Jan -Apr (Box Box 100)
    - 1978 May -Jul (Box Box 100)
    - 1978 Aug -Dec (Box Box 100)
    - Campaign Questionnaires, 1978 (Box Box 100)
  - Subseries D: Manassas National Battlefiled Park Bill
    - HR 5048: Sponsored - 8/1/79 Manassas National Battlefield Park Bill (Box Box 101)
    - MNBP - Correspondence, 1975 (Box Box 101)
    - MNBP - Correspondence, 1976; (2 folders) (Box Box 101)
    - MNBP - Correspondence, 1977 (Box Box 101)
    - MNBP - Correspondence, 1978 (Box Box 102)
    - MNBP - Correspondence, 1979 (Box Box 102)
    - MNBP - Correspondence, 1980 & n.d. (Box Box 102)
    - Manassas National Battlefield Park Bill - Correspondence, 1975-1980 (Box Box 102)
    - MNBP - Maps, 1975-1980 (Box Box 102)
    - MNBP - Miscellaneous, 1975-1979 (Box Box 102)
    - MNBP Bill - 94th, 95th, & 96th Congress, 1975-1980 (Box Box 103)
    - MNBP - Petitions, 1978 (Box Box 103)
    - MNBP - Press Clippings, n.d. (Box Box 103)
    - Manassas Battlefield - 1979 Clips, n.d. (Box Box 103)
    - Gains Support for Manassas Battlefield Bill, 8/1/75 (Box Box 103)
    - Hearings on Harris Manassas Battlefield Bill, 2/17/76 (Box Box 103)
    - Harris Says Speculators Trying to Battlefield Bill, 5/26/76 (Box Box 103)
    - Scott/ Battlefield Editorials, n.d (Box Box 103)
    - Harris Renews Manassas Battlefield Fight (Reintroduction Bill), 1/26/77 (Box Box 103)
    - Interior Subcommittee Approved Harris Manassas Park Bill, 5/24/77 (Box Box 103)
    - House Approved Harris Manassas Park Bill, 6/6/77 (Box Box 103)
    - Senate Subcommittee Considers Harris Manassas Park Bill, 6/28/77 (Box Box 103)
    - Harris Manassas Park Bill Added to Omnibus Parks Bill, 7/10/78 (Box Box 103)
    - Harris Urges Senate Lobby Effort on Manassas Bill, 4/29/79 (Box Box 103)
    - Harris/ Warner Meeting on Manassas Battlefield, 6/22/79 (Box Box 103)
    - Harris Renews Fight to Save Manassas Battlefield, 8/1/79 (Box Box 103)
    - House Holds Hearing on Manassas Bill, 9/6/79 (Box Box 103)
    - House Passes Harris Manassas Bill, 10/9/79 (Box Box 103)
    - Senate Hearing on Manassas Battlefield, 9/3/80 (Box Box 103)
    - Senate Committee OKs Battlefield Bill Vote, 9/17/80 (Box Box 103)
    - Senate Passes Manassas Battlefield Bill, 9/29/80 (Box Box 103)
    - Congress Approves Manassas Bill, 10/1/80 (Box Box 103)
    - MNBP - Senate & House Hearings, 1979-1980 (Box Box 104)
  - Subseries E: Tenants Tax Justice Bill
    - HR 13574, 13306, 13778: Tenants Tax Deduction Bill (Box Box 104)
    - HR 84: Sponsored - 1/4/77 (383-1676) Tax Justice for Tenants (Box Box 104)
    - no record #: Tenants tax bill sponsored 95th Congress (Box Box 104)
    - HR 2191: Sponsored - 2/15/79 Tenant Tax Act (Box Box 104)
    - HR 10219: Tenants Bill Letters/ Dear Colleagues (Box Box 104)
    - HR 10219: Tenants Bill persons HRs/ Cong's names/ interested (Box Box 104)
    - Tenants' Tax Justice Bill - Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box Box 104)
    - Seeks Tax Break for Apartment Renters, 10/17/75 (Box Box 104)
    - Apartment "Life" article Reprint Permission, 3/25/76 (Box Box 104)
    - Harris Gains Support for Tenants Bill, 4/15/76 (Box Box 104)
    - Hope for Tenants Bill '77 (Buckley Amendment) Press Release, 9/27/76 (Box Box 104)
    - Harris Renews Push for Tenants Tax, 1/4/77 (Box Box 104)
    - Harris Says Tax Bill Unfair to Tenants, 8/7/78 (Box Box 104)
    - HR 10219: Tenants Bill Press Releases News Articles (Box Box 104)
    - HR 10219: Tenants Bill Reports and Statements (Box Box 104)
    - no rec. #: Tenants Tax Bill (resource info) (Box Box 104)
- Series IV: Photographs
  - Photographs, 1975-1980; (2 folders) (Box Box 104)
- Series V: Oversized Items
  - 1) Organizational Chart for Internal Revenue Service (Box Oversize)
  - 2) Parking Lot Diagram (Box Oversize)
  - 3) Organizational Chart for FDIC (Box Oversize)
  - 4) Map Depicting Rail Lines in Virginia (Box Oversize)
  - 5) Boundary Maps of Manassas National Battlefield (Box Oversize)
  - 6) Aerial Perspective of the Wheeler International Trade and Convention Center (Box Oversize)
  - 7) Grid Map of Washington D.C. and Vicinity (Box Oversize)
  - 8) Aeronautical Chart for Washington Area (Box Oversize)
  - 9) VFR Terminal Area Chart - Washington (Box Oversize)
  - 10) Jacksonville Sectional Aeronautical Chart (Box Oversize)
  - 11) Index to Topographic Maps of Virginia (Box Oversize)
- Series VI: Restricted
  - Applications and Resumes (A-H), 1977-1978 (Box Box 105)
  - Applications and Resumes (I-M), 1978 (Box Box 105)
  - Applications and Resumes (P-Z), 1977-1978 (Box Box 105)
  - Army, Department of - Salaries, etc., 1979 (Box Box 106)
  - Defense, Department of - Salaries, etc., 1978 (Box Box 106)
  - Recommendations, Applications, etc., 1979 (Box Box 106)
  - Recommendations, Applications, etc., 1980 (Box Box 106)
  - Resumes, 1975-1980; (2 folders) (Box Box 106)
  - Summer Internships, 1977-1978 (Box Box 107)
  - Summer Internships, 1979-1980 (Box Box 107)
  - U.S. House of Representatives Annual Report on Actions Taken in grades GS-16, GS- 17, GS-18; format 2, book 1, 1978; (3 folders) (Box Box 107)
  - U.S. House of Representatives... format 2, book 2, 1978 (Box Box 107)